Tan, Yudistira Suryakencana Adisatria

Semarang, Central Java, 50171 +6289 508 850 613 | <u>yudi.adisatria@gmail.com</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/yudi-adisatria</u> | <u>github.com/YudiAdisatria</u>



Profile

An enthusiastic, organized and hard-working person equipped with strong interpersonal skills, strong motivation to succeed, integrity, dedication, perseverance, and supporting experiences. Graduate on 2022 from Informatics Engineering of Computer Science department at Soegijapranata Catholic University. I have some experiences on several lecturer project especially on web development using Laravel focus on backend engineer to provide database MySQL architecture, functional website, and more.

Eminence & Skill

- SQL (MySql, PGQL)
- PHP Laravel
- JavaScript (DiscordJS, ReactJS)
- Analysis & Debugging Error

- Team Work
- Presentation
- Indonesia Language (Native)
- English Language (<u>TOEFL B1</u>)

Experience

Competency Profile for Bachelor of Psychology Lecturer Project

Website Developer [demo]

Soegijapranata Catholic University, Semarang June 2022 – July 2022

- Internal website on Faculty of Psychology Soegijapranata Catholic University that generates
 competency profile report of the students. Grade points from each Psychology student are
 categorized into several competencies through database MySQL. The website provides
 importing students' data and grades, making the report, and managing access for users into the
 website.
- Analyze the old system and develop the new system that provide client needs. Planning, analyzing, and executing the project.

Assets Management on Atmodirono Church Lecturer Project

Soegijapranata Catholic University, Semarang April 2022 – June 2022

Website Developer – Backend Engineer [demo]

 Website for assets management in Atmodirono Church. This website was made for internal organization. Provides CRUD for assets, category, buildings and each room, users, and reports (history of moving asset and assets in a room) through database MySQL. The website was made with Laravel 8 and laravel excel library.

News and E-Magazine Website of PARAGA Soegijapranata Catholic University, Semarang
Website Developer – Backend Engineer [link] [demo] August 2021 – February 2022

Paraga is a student activity unit in Soegijapranata Catholic University that focuses on journalism.
 The website provides creating, reading, updating, and deleting (CRUD) news and e-magazine called Gazebo.

Discord Bot using Discord.Js

Developer [link]

October 2020 - February 2021

Having fun project that follow tutorial on Youtube to create a Discord Bot using Discord.Js. It provide moderation, game, and admin commands.

Education

Soegijapranata Catholic University, Computer Science *Bachelor of Informatics Engineering - GPA 3,99* [CGPA]

Semarang, Central Java 2019 - 2022

- Faculty Student Senate of Computer Science
 Head of Student Senate (2021-2022), Organization and Regeneration (2020-2021), Advocacy (2019-2020)
 - Faculty organization at Soegijapranata Catholic University in the department of Computer Science that run legislative section
 - Run the organization, collaboration with student executive to run several event, meeting with faculty staff, and also collect aspiration from student and deliver to the faculty
- Student Activity Unit Paraga

Director (2021-2022), Chief Editor (2020-2021), Reporter (2019-2020)

- Student activity unit at Soegijapranata Catholic University that has the interest in journalism
- Run the organization, create several events, become editorial team for news publication, and make news about university or other student activity units' event

Loyola College Senior High School Semarang *Science*

Semarang, Central Java

2016 - 2019

SERIGALA

High school extracurricular in journalism

- Leader(2017-2018), Reporter (2016-2018)
- o Run the organization, supervisor to every news on school newspaper

Awards and Achievements

Student of the Year 2021

Soegijapranata Catholic University

Top 10

Winner

August 2021

Competition held to find the student of the year 2021 in Soegijapranata Catholic University

Student of the Year of Faculty Computer Science 2021

Soegijapranata Catholic University May 2021

• Competition held to find the delegate from Faculty to compete in university level

Reporter on school.tribunjateng.com Reporter

Loyola College Senior High School Semarang January 2019

 An award for my contribution as a reporter during the year of 2018 for SMA Kolese Loyola on school.tribunjateng.com